Guide to the Boone and Crockett Club Records circa 1885-2009
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Administration, 1888-2007; Series I; 45.5 linear feet
  - Officers and Committees, 1888-2005; Subseries 4; 14.75 linear feet
    - Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1888-2005; Sub-subseries 2; 8.5 linear feet
      - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1953-1965 (Box-folder 36/4-5)
      - Correspondence, Memoranda and Reports, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 36/6-7)
      - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 36/8)
      - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1982 (Box-folder 37/1)
      - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 37/2)
      - Fairman R. Dick, Correspondence, 1956-1960 (Box-folder 37/3-4)
      - Fairman R. Dick, Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 37/5-6)
      - Draft Financial Statements, 1989 (Box-folder 37/7)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Agenda, 1988 (Box-folder 37/8)
      - Karl Frederick, Vice President and Executive Committee, Correspondence, 1937-1951 (Box-folder 37/9-10)
      - Henry G. Gray, Correspondence, 1921-1937 (Box-folder 38/1)
      - Long-Range Strategy and Work Plan, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 38/2)
      - Meeting Agendas, 1953-1959 (Box-folder 38/3)
      - Meeting Agendas, 1962-1975 (Box-folder 38/4-5)
      - Meeting Agendas and Meeting Materials, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 38/6-7)
      - Conference Call Meeting Agenda, 1994 (Box-folder 38/8)
      - Meeting Attendance, 1988 (Box-folder 38/9)
      - Meeting Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 38/10)
      - Meeting Materials, 1981 (Box-folder 38/11)
      - Meeting Materials, 1992 (Box-folder 38/12)
      - Meeting Materials, 1993 (Box-folder 39/1)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1888-1889 (Box-folder 39/2)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1897-1902 (Box-folder 39/3)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 39/4)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1906 (Box-folder 39/5)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1907 (Box-folder 39/6)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1908-1913 (Box-folder 39/7-8)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1919-1923 (Box-folder 39/9)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1923-1928 (Box-folder 39/10)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1929-1934 (Box-folder 39/11)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1935-1939 (Box-folder 40/1)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1940-1944 (Box-folder 40/2)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1945-1949 (Box-folder 40/3)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 40/4)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 40/5)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1955 (Box-folder 40/6)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1956 (Box-folder 40/7)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1957 (Box-folder 41/1-2)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1958 (Box-folder 41/3)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1959 (Box-folder 41/4)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1960 (Box-folder 41/5)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1961 (Box-folder 41/6)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1962 (Box-folder 41/7-8)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1963 (Box-folder 42/1)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1964 (Box-folder 42/2)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 42/3-6)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1967 (Box-folder 43/1-2)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1968 (Box-folder 43/3-4)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1969 (Box-folder 43/5-6)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1970 (Box-folder 43/7-9)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1971 (Box-folder 44/1-4)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box-folder 44/5-6 (1-2 of 3))
      - Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box-folder 45/1 (3 of 3))
      - Meeting Minutes, 1973 (Box-folder 45/2-5)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1974 (Box-folder 45/6-7 (1-2 of 4))
      - Meeting Minutes, 1974 (Box-folder 46/1-2 (3-4 of 4))
      - Meeting Minutes, 1975 (Box-folder 46/3-5)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1976 (Box-folder 46/6-7 (1-2 of 4))
      - Meeting Minutes, 1976 (Box-folder 47/1-2 (3-4 of 4))
      - Meeting Minutes, 1977 (Box-folder 47/3-5)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1978 (Box-folder 47/6-8)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1979 (Box-folder 48/1-3)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1980 (Box-folder 48/4-5)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1981 (Box-folder 48/6)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1982 (Box-folder 48/7-8)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box-folder 49/1-2)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box-folder 49/3)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 49/4-6)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box-folder 49/7)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box-folder 49/8)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 50/1)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box-folder 50/2)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 50/3)
      - Meeting Minutes, 2000 (Box-folder 50/4)
      - Meeting Minutes, Summary by Shannon Peterson, 1994 (Box-folder 50/5-6)
      - Meeting Minutes Summaries, 1930-1969, 1996 (Box-folder 50/7)
      - Meeting Minutes Summaries, 1970-1996 (Box-folder 50/8)
      - Meeting Minutes, Template, undated (Box-folder 51/1)
      - Meeting, North Carolina, 1992 (Box-folder 51/2)
      - Meeting Notes, Author Unknown, 1973 (Box-folder 51/3)
      - Officer and Committee Descriptions and Policies and Procedures Manual, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 51/4)
      - Open Meeting at The University Club, Correspondence, Memoranda, Meeting Minutes, and Meeting Materials, 1980 (Box-folder 51/5)
      - Organizing Meeting, Minutes, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 51/6)
      - Gifford Pinchot, Correspondence, 1902 (Box-folder 51/7)
      - Reports, 1888-1923 (Box-folder 51/8)
      - Resolutions, 1897 (Box-folder 51/9)
      - Reports and Resolutions, 1901-1902 (Box-folder 51/10)
      - Resolution, Cook Forest, Pennsylvania, undated (Box-folder 51/11)
      - Resolutions, 1919 and undated (Box-folder 51/12)
      - Resolutions, 1931-1932 (Box-folder 51/13)
      - Resolutions, 1951-1962 (Box-folder 51/14)
      - Rosters, 1946-1960 (Box-folder 51/15)
      - Rosters, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 51/16)
      - Roster, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 51/17)
      - William G. Sheldon, Correspondence, undated (Box-folder 51/18)
      - Strategic Plan, 1992 (Box-folder 51/19)
      - Strategic Plan, Work Papers, 1992 (Box-folder 51/20)
      - Strategic Plan, 1993 (Box-folder 51/21)
      - Strategic Plan, Galley Proofs and Draft, 1992 (Box-folder OS 219/x)
      - Strategic Plan, Work Papers, 1999 (Box-folder 234/3)
      - Technology Plan, 2001 (Box-folder 229/9)
      - White House Meeting, Group Photographs, 1988 (Box-folder 51/22)
      - Lawrence C. Woods, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1963-1973 (Box-folder 51/23)
    - Other Administrative Committees, 1950-2005; Sub-subseries 3; 0.5 linear feet
      This sub-subseries contains administrative committee materials not created by the executive committee. Materials include correspondence, minutes, and reports.
      - Ad Hoc Committee on Purposes and Future Direction, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1957-1975 (Box-folder 52/1)
      - Administrative Guidance Committee, Correspondence, Memoranda, and Minutes, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 52/2-4)
      - Advisory Board, Conference Call Meeting Minutes, 2004 (Box-folder 225/1)
      - Executive Planning Team, Meeting Materials, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 228/1)
      - Finance Study Committee, Correspondence, Memoranda, and Reports, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 52/5)
      - House Committee, Correspondence, 1911 (Box-folder 234/4)
      - Investment Committee Report, 1975 (Box-folder 52/6)
      - Investment Committee, Report, 1976 (Box-folder 52/7)
      - Policy Advisory Committee, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1960 (Box-folder 52/8)
      - Reception Committee, Correspondence and Miscellaneous Materials, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 52/9)
      - Special Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1950 (Box-folder 52/10)
      - Strategic Planning Committee, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1994 (Box-folder 52/11)
      - Transition Committee, Meeting Minutes and Notes, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 52/12)
  - Member Meetings, 1894-2007; Subseries 5; 5.75 linear feet
    Annual membership gatherings have been a cornerstone of the Club since its inception. The founding members believed that meetings and discussions between members kept the membership active and engaged in conservation issues. This subseries has been divided into three sub-subseries.
    - Annual Meetings and Dinners, 1894-2007; Sub-subseries 1; 3.75 linear feet
      This sub-subseries contains the minutes of over 100 years of the Club’s annual meetings, which document membership involvement in the conservation, big game records keeping, and foundation goals of the Club.
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1894-1903 (Box-folder 53/1)
      - Annual Dinner, Attendants List, 1903 (Box-folder 53/2)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1904-1906 (Box-folder 53/3)
      - Annual Meeting, Attendants List and Ticket, 1907 (Box-folder 53/4)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1907-1908 (Box-folder 53/5)
      - Annual Meeting, Materials, 1911 (Box-folder 53/6)
      - Annual Meeting, Notices, 1915 (Box-folder 53/7)
      - Annual Dinner, Attendants Lists, 1918 (Box-folder 53/8)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1918-1922 (Box-folder 53/9)
      - Annual Meeting, Materials, 1920 (Box-folder 53/10)
      - Annual Meeting, Materials, 1921 (Box-folder 53/11)
      - Annual Meeting, Materials, 1922 (Box-folder 53/12)
      - Annual Meeting, Materials, 1923 (Box-folder 53/13)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1923-1929 (Box-folder 53/14)
      - Annual Meeting, Materials, 1924 (Box-folder 53/15)
      - Annual Meeting, Materials, 1925 (Box-folder 53/16)
      - Annual Meeting, Materials, 1927 (Box-folder 53/17)
      - Annual Meeting and Dinner, Announcements, 1929-1970 (Box-folder 53/18)
      - Annual Dinner, Menu, 1930 (Box-folder 53/19)
      - Annual Meeting, Materials, 1931 (Box-folder 53/20)
      - Annual Meeting, Notices and Invitations, 1936-1958 (Box-folder 53/21)
      - Annual Dinner, Menus, 1938-1949 (Box-folder 53/22)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1938-1949 (Box-folder 53/23)
      - Annual Dinner and Luncheon, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 54/1)
      - Annual Dinner, Menus, 1950-1959 (Box-folder 54/2)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1950-1955 (Box-folder 54/3-4)
      - Annual Dinner, Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 54/5)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 54/6)
      - Annual Dinner, Attendants List, 1957 (Box-folder 54/7)
      - Annual Dinners and Luncheons, Planning Materials, 1957-1962 (Box-folder 54/8)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1959 (Box-folder 54/9)
      - Annual Dinner, Menu and Member Mailer, 1960 (Box-folder 55/1)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1960 (Box-folder 55/2)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1961 (Box-folder 55/3)
      - Annual Dinner, Correspondence, Memoranda, and Menus, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 55/4)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 55/5)
      - Annual Dinner, Menus and Programs, 1962-1971 (Box-folder 55/6)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 55/7-8)
      - Annual Meeting, Agendas and Invitations, 1965-1990 (Box-folder 56/1)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1966 (Box-folder 56/2)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1967 (Box-folder 56/3)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1968-1979 (Box-folder 56/4)
      - Annual Meeting, Derek Stonorov, Presentation, 1970 (Box-folder 56/5)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 56/6)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 56/7)
      - Annual Dinner and Luncheon, Attendants Lists, 1973 (Box-folder 56/8)
      - Annual Dinner, Menu, 1973 (Box-folder 56/9)
      - Annual Meeting and Dinner, Agendas, Correspondence, and Memoranda, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 56/10)
      - Annual Meeting and Dinner, Attendants Lists, Correspondence, and Memoranda, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 56/11)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 56/12)
      - Annual Dinner, Jack S. Parker, Correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 56/13)
      - Annual Meeting, Committee Reports and Memoranda, 1979 (Box-folder 56/14)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 57/1)
      - Annual Luncheon, Minutes, 1980 (Box-folder 57/2)
      - Annual Meeting, Committee Reports, Correspondence, and Memoranda, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 57/3)
      - Annual Meeting, Agendas and Member Responses, 1981 (Box-folder 57/4)
      - Annual Meeting, Attendants List, 1981 (Box-folder 57/5)
      - Annual Meeting, Agendas, Correspondence, Meeting Materials, and Memoranda, 1982 (Box-folder 57/6)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1982 (Box-folder 57/7)
      - Annual Meeting, Planning, 1982 (Box-folder 57/8)
      - Annual Dinner, Menus and Programs, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 57/9)
      - Annual Meeting, Agendas, Correspondence, Meeting Materials, 1984 (Box-folder 57/10)
      - Annual Meeting, Attendants List, 1984 (Box-folder 57/11)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes and Schedules, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 57/12)
      - Annual Dinner and Luncheon, Attendants Lists, 1987 (Box-folder 57/13)
      - Annual Meeting, Materials, 1988 (Box-folder 57/14)
      - Annual Meeting, Attendants Lists, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 57/15)
      - Annual Meeting, Planning, 1990 (Box-folder 57/16)
      - Annual Meeting, Agendas and Invitations, 1991 (Box-folder 57/17)
      - Annual Dinner, Invitations, 1991 (Box-folder 57/18)
      - Annual Meeting, Meeting Packet, 1991 (Box-folder 57/19)
      - Annual Dinner, Menus, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 57/20)
      - Annual Meeting, Planning, 1991 (Box-folder 57/21)
      - Annual Meeting, Agenda, 1992 (Box-folder 57/22)
      - Annual Meeting, Materials, 1992 (Box-folder 58/1)
      - Annual Meeting, Meeting Packet, 1992 (Box-folder 58/2)
      - Annual Meeting, Planning, 1992 (Box-folder 58/3)
      - Annual Meeting, Planning, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 58/4)
      - Annual Meeting, Meeting Packet, 1993 (Box-folder 58/5)
      - Annual Meeting, Materials, 1994 (Box-folder 58/6)
      - Annual Meeting, Meeting Packet, 1994 (Box-folder 58/7)
      - Hal Salwasser, Annual Meeting Speech, 1994 (Box-folder 58/8)
      - Annual Meeting, Correspondence, Memoranda, and Miscellaneous Materials, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 58/9-10)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1995 (Box-folder 58/11)
      - Annual Meeting, Agendas, Meeting Minutes, and Schedules, 1996 (Box-folder 59/1)
      - Annual Meeting, Agendas, Meeting Minutes, and Schedules, 1997 (Box-folder 59/2)
      - Annual Meeting, Planning, 1997 (Box-folder 59/3)
      - Annual Meeting, Agendas and Committee Schedules, 1998 (Box-folder 59/4)
      - Annual Meeting, Attendants Lists, 1998 (Box-folder 59/5)
      - Annual Meeting, Planning, 1998 (Box-folder 59/6)
      - Annual Meeting, Agenda, 1999 (Box-folder 59/7)
      - Annual Meeting, Auction Items, 1999 (Box-folder 59/8)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1999 (Box-folder 59/9)
      - Annual Meeting, Materials, 2000 (Box-folder 59/10-11)
      - Annual Meeting, Schedule, 2000 (Box-folder 59/12)
      - Annual Dinner, Attendants List, undated (Box-folder 59/13)
      - Annual Meeting, Slide Program for Hunting Hall of Fame Award, undated (Box-folder 59/14)
      - Annual Auction, Correpondence, Invoices and Receipts, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 227/4)
      - Annual Meeting, Correspondence, Memoranda, and Meeting Materials, 2001 (Box-folder 228/11-12)
      - Annual Auction, Donation Solicitation, Correspondence, 2001 (Box-folder 227/3)
      - Annual Auction, Item List, 2001 (Box-folder 230/10)
      - Annual Meeting, Agenda and Committee Schedules, 2002 (Box-folder 225/13)
      - Annual Meeting, Correspondence, Itineraries, and Memoranda, 2002 (Box-folder 225/14 (1 of 2))
      - Annual Meeting, Correspondence, Itineraries, and Memoranda, 2002 (Box-folder 230/1 (2 of 2))
      - Annual Meeting, Itineraries and Reservations, 2002 (Box-folder 225/12)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, Initial Draft, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 225/10)
      - Annual Meeting, Agendas, Attendance, and Registration Confirmation, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 225/11)
      - Annual Dinner, Menus, 2007 (Box-folder 225/6)
    - Centennial Celebration, 1982-1989; Sub-subseries 2; 0.5 linear feet
      This sub-subseries includes planning materials, correspondence, and committee materials related to the Club’s Centennial Celebration which took place in 1988 in Dallas, Texas.
      - Agenda and Invitations, 1988 (Box-folder 59/15)
      - Auction, 1988 (Box-folder 59/16)
      - Auction Items, Receipts, 1988 (Box-folder 59/17)
      - Auction, Item List and Program, 1988 (Box-folder 59/18)
      - Centennial Celebration Committee, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1987 (Box-folder 59/19)
      - Centennial Celebration Committee, Meeting Minutes and Meeting Materials, 1982 (Box-folder 59/20)
      - Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 59/21)
      - Sherman Gray, Correspondence, 1988 (Box-folder 59/22)
      - Projects, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 59/23)
      - Ruger Boone and Crockett Club Centennial Rifles, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 59/24)
      - Ruger Magnum Rifle Packet, 1988 (Box-folder 60/1)
      - Sagamore Hill Dinner, Correspondence, 1988 (Box-folder 60/2)
      - Sagamore Hill Meeting, 1988 (Box-folder 60/3)
    - Other Member Meetings, 1902-2003; Sub-subseries 3; 1.5 linear feet
      In addition to the Club’s annual meetings, membership was often invited to attend casual meetings throughout the year. In the early years of the Club these meetings included presentations and slideshows of hunts by individual members. Later, the Club moved to have membership officially meet quarterly. This sub-subseries contains meeting minutes, correspondence, and planning materials for these events.
      - Dinner, Exhibition of Photographs and Descriptions by Members, Ledger, 1902 (Box-folder 60/4)
      - Dinner, Guest Response Form and Member Mailer, 1908 (Box-folder 60/5)
      - Izaak Walton Dinner, Recipes Collected, 1945 (Box-folder 60/6)
      - Siemel Film Showing, Correspondence, 1952 (Box-folder 60/7)
      - Informal Member Meeting, Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 60/8)
      - Sagamore Hill Meeting, Photographs, 1955 (Box-folder 60/9)
      - Spring Quarterly Meeting at Sagamore Hill, Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 60/10)
      - Spring Quarterly Meeting at Sagamore Hill, Correspondence and Meeting Materials, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 60/11)
      - Spring Quarterly Meeting at Sagamore Hill, Member Mailers, 1956-1961 (Box-folder 60/12)
      - Spring Quarterly Meeting at Sagamore Hill, Planning Materials, 1956 (Box-folder 60/13)
      - Spring Quarterly Meeting at Sagamore Hill, Correspondence and Meeting Materials, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 60/14)
      - Sagamore Hill Meetings, Correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 60/15)
      - Special Meeting, Correspondence, 1982 (Box-folder 60/16)
      - 4th of July Float, Cody, Wyoming, 1991 (Box-folder 60/17)
      - Special Meeting, Minutes, 1992 (Box-folder 60/18)
      - March Meeting, Materials, 1994 (Box-folder 60/19)
      - June Meeting, Materials, 1994 (Box-folder 60/20)
      - Fall Quarterly Meeting, Committee Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box-folder 61/1)
      - Spring Quarterly Meeting, Planning Materials, 1995 (Box-folder 61/2)
      - Spring Quarterly Meeting, Planning Materials, 1996 (Box-folder 61/3)
      - Fall Quarterly Meeting, Materials, 1996 (Box-folder 61/4)
      - Spring Quarterly Meeting, Planning Materials, 1997 (Box-folder 61/5)
      - Fall Quarterly Meeting, Materials, 1997 (Box-folder 61/6)
      - Spring Quarterly Meeting, Planning Materials, 1998 (Box-folder 61/7)
      - Fall Quarterly Meeting, Materials, 1998 (Box-folder 61/8)
      - Spring Quarterly Meeting, Agenda and Schedule, 1999 (Box-folder 61/9)
      - Spring Quarterly Meeting, Minutes, 1999 (Box-folder 61/10)
      - Spring Quarterly Meeting, Planning Materials, 1999 (Box-folder 61/11)
      - Summer Quarterly Meeting, Minutes, 1999 (Box-folder 61/12)
      - Fall Quarterly Meeting, Materials, 1999 (Box-folder 61/13)
      - Fall Quarterly Meeting, Minutes, 1999 (Box-folder 61/14)
      - Spring Quarterly Meeting, Planning Materials, 2000 (Box-folder 62/1)
      - Fall Quarterly Meeting, Materials, 2000 (Box-folder 62/2)
      - Summer Meeting, Guest Response Forms, 2001 (Box-folder 227/1)
      - Summer Meeting, Materials, 2001 (Box-folder 227/6-7)
      - Fall Meeting, Itineraries and Memoranda, 2001 (Box-folder 230/6)
      - Summer Meeting, Correspondence, Itineraries and Memoranda, 2002 (Box-folder 230/9)
      - Spring Meeting, Itineraries and Memoranda, 2003 (Box-folder 230/7)
      - Fall Meeting, Attendance List, 2003 (Box-folder 228/3)
      - Texas Members of Boone and Crockett Club, Member Meeting, Memoranda and Resolutions, 2003 (Box-folder 230/8)
  - Membership, 1899-2007; Subseries 6; 6.50 linear feet
    This subseries contains minutes, correspondence, member mailers, membership election ballots, and Membership Committee materials. The subseries includes almost an entire run of Club yearbooks which document Club membership, officers, and committee involvement dating from 1906 to the present. The subseries also documents the process for obtaining regular membership as it includes membership endorsements and sponsorships.
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Membership Policy, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 62/3)
    - Berry B. Brooks, Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 62/4)
    - Candidates for Membership, Abandoned, 1949-1958 (Box-folder 62/5)
    - Jay Norwood "Ding" Darling, Honorary Club Membership, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 62/6)
    - Dues, Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 62/7)
    - Dues Notices, A-L, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 62/8)
    - Dues Notices, M-Z, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 62/9)
    - Dues Notices and Membership Lists, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 62/10)
    - Dues Notices, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 62/11)
    - Emeritus Membership, Accepted, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 62/12)
    - Former Member Lists, undated (Box-folder 62/13)
    - Sherman Gray, Notes, 1977 (Box-folder 62/14)
    - Map of Membership, 1993 (Box-folder 62/15)
    - Member Notices, 1972-1981 (Box-folder 62/16)
    - Member Survey Responses, 1996 (Box-folder 63/1)
    - Members, Biographical Information, circa 1978 (Box-folder 63/2)
    - Membership and Dues, Correspondence, 1980-1991 (Box-folder 63/3)
    - Membership and Meeting Forms, Originals, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 63/4)
    - Membership Candidate Dossiers, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 63/5)
    - Membership Candidates, Elected and Withdrawn, 1896-1901 (Box-folder 63/6)
    - Membership Card Catalog, 1968-1970 (Box 220)
    - Membership Changes, 1901-1946 (Box-folder 63/7)
    - Membership Committee, Candidates, Not Qualified, 1950-1974 (Box-folder 63/8-10)
    - Membership Committee, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1969 (Box-folder 64/1)
    - Membership Committee, Correspondence, Memoranda, and Reports, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 64/2-3)
    - Membership Committee, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 64/4-5)
    - Membership Committee, Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 64/6-8)
    - Membership Committee, Correspondence and Memorandum, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 65/1)
    - Membership Committee, Delinquent Dues, 1983 (Box-folder 65/2)
    - Membership Committee, Emeritus Status Requests, 1992 (Box-folder 65/3)
    - Membership Committee, Robert M. Ferguson, Correspondence, 1977 (Box-folder 65/4)
    - Membership Committee, Meeting Agendas and Membership Policies, 1948-1976 (Box-folder 65/5)
    - Membership Committee, Meeting Agenda, 1999 (Box-folder 65/6)
    - Membership Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 65/7)
    - Membership Committee, Member Status Changes, Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 65/8)
    - Membership Committee, Memoranda and Reports, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 65/9)
    - Membership Committee, Memoranda, 1999 (Box-folder 65/10)
    - Membership, Correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 65/11)
    - Membership, Correspondence, 1942-1961 (Box-folder 65/12-15)
    - Membership, Correspondence, 1989 (Box-folder 65/16)
    - Membership, Correspondence, 2003 (Box-folder 230/2)
    - Membership Directory, Changes, 1951-1961 (Box-folder 65/17)
    - Membership Directory, Changes, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 65/18)